Guide to the Yale-China Association Administrative Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Administrative records, 1906-1989; Accession 1991-A-035
  - Seventy-Fifth Anniversary Dinner, 2/1975-2/1976 (Box 50, Folder 737)
  - Speeches from the 75th Anniversary Dinner of 2/7/1976, 2/1976-5/1976 (Box 50, Folder 738)
  - Seventy-Fifth Anniversary Planning. Committee Meeting on June 10, 5/1975 (Box 50, Folder 739)
  - Seventy-Fifth Anniversary Guest List, 2/7/1976 (Box 50, Folder 740)
  - Shepard, Charles, 5/1971-9/1973, 9/23/1971-5/23/1973 (Box 50, Folder 741-742)
  - Shepard, Charles, 1/4/1973-9/17/1975, Prior to 8/1980 (Box 51, Folder 743-744)
  - Shove, John D., 6/27/1980-9/26/1980 (Box 51, Folder 745)
  - Sim, Yawsoon (Former Overseas Scholarship Holder), 4/1974 (Box 51, Folder 746)
  - Smith, Dwight C., 3/2/1984 (Box 51, Folder 747)
  - Smith, Harlod (Former Staff), 1982-1986 (Box 51, Folder 748)
  - Smith, Robert A. (Former Trustee), 12/26/1973-1/12/1982 (Box 51, Folder 749)
  - Solicitation-Appeal Letters and Flyers, 1977-1978 (Box 51, Folder 750)
  - Sample Solicitation Letters, 2/1976-6/1977 (Box 51, Folder 751)
  - Solicitation: Classes, 45W, 3/1976-5/1976 (Box 51, Folder 752)
  - Solicitation: Envelope, 12/1975 (Box 51, Folder 753)
  - Solicitation, 4/75-10/1975 (Box 51, Folder 754)
  - Solicitation: Procedure, Schedule, 1972-1976 (Box 51, Folder 755)
  - Solicitation Lists: Big Givers, 3/21/1973-11/1/1974 (Box 51, Folder 756)
  - Speaking Engagements, 10/11/1967-3/9/1977 (Box 51, Folder 757)
  - Special Committee to choose Lovett Successor, 6/15/1964-2/6/1965 (Box 51, Folder 758)
  - Spelman, Douglas: Annual Report, 5/8/1976-7/31/1976 (Box 51, Folder 759)
  - Spelman, Douglas: Interim Report, Field, 2/8/1975-5/1976 (Box 51, Folder 760)
  - Spelman, Douglas: Representative Correspondence, 12/1973-6/30/1975 (Box 51, Folder 761)
  - Spelman, Douglas: Representative, 1/24/1974-12/30/1974 (Box 51, Folder 762)
  - Spelman, Douglas: Representative Correspondence (1 of 2), 6/9/1975-6/18/1976 (Box 52, Folder 763)
  - Spelman, Douglas: Representative Correspondence (2 of 2), 6/22/1976-8/21/1976 (Box 52, Folder 764)
  - Spelman, Douglas: Representative Correspondence, 8/23/1976-8/30/1976, 12/17/1976-4/15/1977 (Box 52, Folder 765-766)
  - Spelman, Douglas: Representative, 6/22/1977-10/19/1977 (Box 52, Folder 767)
  - Standing Committees (Lists of), 1964-1974 (Box 52, Folder 768)
  - Standing Committee, 1973-1975, 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 769-770)
  - Statement of the Development of Higher Education for the Free Chinese of Hong Kong and Southeast Asia (Box 52, Folder 771)
  - Steering Committee Lists, 1971-1973 (Box 52, Folder 772)
  - Steering Committee Meetings: Related Materials, 10/26/1971-10/23/1973 (Box 52, Folder 773)
  - Steering Committee: Items For Agenda, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 774)
  - Steering Committee Minutes, 12/11/1971-4/29/1973 (Box 53, Folder 775)
  - Stokes, Rev. Anson Phillips, Jr. (Trustee), 3/6/1975-6/19/1985 (Box 53, Folder 776)
  - "The Strategic Implications of U. S. Arms Sales to China", 1/18/1982-2/2/1982 (Box 53, Folder 777)
  - Student Christian Center: Hong Kong, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 778)
  - Student Committee, 8/12/1973-6/23/1974, 4/16/1980-10/30/1980, 4/9/1980-4/26/1982, 1982-1986 (Box 53, Folder 779-785)
  - Students from the PRC to the U. S., 8/17/1978-10/17/1978 (Box 53, Folder 786)
  - Sturbridge Village Trip, 7/1980 (Box 53, Folder 787)
  - Sweet, Sidney (Trustee), 1/17/1973-7/3/1979 (Box 53, Folder 788)
  - "T", 8/13/1972-12/21/1978 (Box 53, Folder 789)
  - Talbot, Patrick Memorial Fund, 1/16/1980-4/28/1982 (Box 53, Folder 790)
  - Tam Mai-Sie, 1972-1974 (Box 53, Folder 791)
  - Tang, Lung Wai (Overseas Scholar-Sociology), 1974-1976 (Box 53, Folder 792)
  - Thank-you's, 3/12/1974-1/30/1975 (Box 53, Folder 793)
  - Thayer, Nelson S.T. (Rev), 7/1966-8/3/1990 (Box 53, Folder 794)
  - Thomson, Dean Keith S., 5/26/1981-5/5/1982 (Box 54, Folder 795)
  - Ticket Sales Procedure, 3/9/1974-8/29/1975 (Box 54, Folder 796)
  - Tours 1979 (Box 54, Folder 797)
  - Tours 1980 (Box 54, Folder 798)
  - Tours 1981, Spring (Box 54, Folder 799)
  - Tours 1981, Fall (Box 54, Folder 800)
  - Trustee Correspondence, 1/8/1971-1/11/1973, 12/13/1972-8/20/1973, 2/1974-5/10/1974 (Box 54, Folder 801-803)
  - Trustee Correspondence, 1976-1979, 1977-1979 (Box 55, Folder 804-805)
  - Trustee Fund Drive: Companies with Subsidiaries in Hong Kong, 1973-1974 (Box 55, Folder 806)
  - Trustee Fund Drive: Original Materials, 1973-1974 (Box 55, Folder 807)
  - Trustee Fund Drive: Foundations with International Interests, 1973-1974 (Box 55, Folder 808)
  - Trustee Fund Drive: Pledges, 12/1973 (Box 55, Folder 809)
  - Trustee Fund Drive: Foundations Giving $100 or More in 1972-1973, 1973-1974 (Box 55, Folder 810)
  - Trustees: Former, Contribution Record, 1962-1974 (Box 55, Folder 811)
  - Trustee Lists, 1965-8/24/1976, 1976-1978 (Box 55, Folder 812-814)
  - Trustees Meetings: Materials For, 4/8/1972-12/2/1973 (Box 55, Folder 815)
  - Trustees Meetings: Minutes From Board, 1948-1965 (Box 55, Folder 816)
  - Trustees Meetings: Minutes, 6/10/1968-11/13/1975 (Box 55, Folder 817)
  - Trustees Meetings, 10/11/1974-6/10/1975, 5/14/1975-8/23/1976, 12/8/1978, 2/17/1978 (Box 55, Folder 818-821)
  - Trustees Meetings: Agenda, Items For, 1977-1979 (Box 56, Folder 822)
  - Trustees, Board of, 1/24/1975-4/1/1976 (Box 56, Folder 823)
  - Trustees, Board Meeting, 10/5/1976-10/20/1977, 10/28/1977 (Box 56, Folder 824-825)
  - Trustees And Officers, 1973-1977 (Box 56, Folder 826)
  - Trustees: Notices to, etc…, 6/13/1966-1/8/1976 (Box 56, Folder 827)
  - Trustees: Special Fund Raising (Telethon), 5/1975-6/1975 (Box 56, Folder 828)
  - Trustees: Quarterly Newsletter, 10/17/1973-5/31/1974 (Box 56, Folder 829)
  - Trustees: Telethon follow up on $100 delinquents and suggested new $100 contracts, 2/1975 (Box 56, Folder 830)
  - Tseng, Hsaing Leu, M.D., 5/18/1955-12/5/1983 (Box 56, Folder 831)
  - Turcotte, Philipe (Treasurer), 10/10/1977-6/1/1985 (Box 56, Folder 832)
  - Turner, J. McCollugh, 6/10/1967-7/19/1967 (Box 56, Folder 833)
  - "U", 11/28/1972-6/9/1975 (Box 56, Folder 834)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, 12/9/1974-4/2/1976, 3/2/1972-10/11/1974 (Box 56, Folder 835-836)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia: Board of Trustees Meeting, 4/8/1974-11/20/1974 (Box 56, Folder 837)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, 1/18/1973-8/23/1975, 1976-1979 (Box 56, Folder 838-839)
  - United College of the Chinese, University of Hong Kong, 1966-8/7/1973 (Box 57, Folder 840)
  - U.S.-China People's Friendship Association, 3/1974-3/10/1978 (Box 57, Folder 841)
  - U.S.-China People's Friendship Association: Sports Night, 10/6/1975-1/1913/1976 (Box 57, Folder 842)
  - United States Programs: The Music of China, 11/28/1977-11/21/1978 (Box 57, Folder 843)
  - U.S. Programs: Video Taped Dance Program, 1/24/1978-5/2/1978 (Box 57, Folder 844)
  - U. S. National Arboretum, U. S. Department of Agriculture, 12/3/1974-12/17/1974 (Box 57, Folder 845)
  - University Health Service, Annual Report (Chinese Univ. of Hong Kong), 1977-1978 (Box 57, Folder 846)
  - Universities Service Center, 3/2/1976-2/13/1984 (Box 57, Folder 847)
  - "V", 9/27/1973-3/17/1976 (Box 57, Folder 848)
  - Vannorsdall, John W (Rev), 2/24/1978-8/26/1982 (Box 57, Folder 849)
  - Videotaping, 4/25/1978-10/10/1979 (Box 57, Folder 850)
  - Visits to PRC, 1973-1976 (Box 57, Folder 851)
  - "W", 12/2/1972-4/10/1979 (Box 57, Folder 852)
  - Wang Ning (Visiting Scholar: Languages), 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder 853)
  - Weaver, Howard S., 12/1973-4/1982 (Box 57, Folder 854)
  - Weekend Bills, 1/4/1974-8/1928/1975 (Box 57, Folder 855)
  - Weigle, Luther (Trustee, Hon), 3/2/1976-9/2/1976 (Box 57, Folder 856)
  - Weigle, Richard D.: Correspondence, 11/1955-9/1956, 1957-1959 (Box 57, Folder 857-859)
  - Weigle, Richard D.: Correspondence, 1960-1967, 1969-1973 (Box 58, Folder 860-865)
  - Weigle, Richard D.: Papers, 1/7/1949-12/21/1976 (Box 58, Folder 866)
  - Weigle, Richard D.: Papers and Correspondence, 1/2/1974-5/24/1978 (Box 58, Folder 867)
  - Weigle, Richard D., 8/18/1981-1/13/1977 (Box 58, Folder 868)
  - Wellesley College: Asian Program Information, 3/17/1970-2/8/1971 (Box 58, Folder 869)
  - West Coast Office, Yale Univ: Frank Schork, Exec. Director, 4/21/1970-4/8/1971 (Box 58, Folder 870)
  - Westerfield, Mr. Putney, 8/22/1969-1/4/1984 (Box 58, Folder 871)
  - Woman's Activities, 1924-1925 (Box 59, Folder 872)
  - Wong, Fai-Ming, Senior Faculty Fellow, 1974-1975 (Box 59, Folder 873)
  - Wong, Wai-Ching, Graduate Scholar, 1970-1972 (Box 59, Folder 874)
  - Wong, Yau-Chuen, Senior Faculty Fellow: Mathematics, 1973-1974 (Box 59, Folder 875)
  - World Studies Data Bank, 4/3/1975 (Box 59, Folder 876)
  - Worthy, Edmund Jr., Rep. Salary Agreement, 1971-1974 (Box 59, Folder 877)
  - Worthy, Edmund Jr., Rep. Duties of, 1969-1970 (Box 59, Folder 878)
  - Worthy, Edmund Jr., Rep. Annual Reports, 1971-1974 (Box 59, Folder 879)
  - Worthy, Edmund Jr., Rep. Interim Reports, 2/1973-11/1973 (Box 59, Folder 880)
  - Worthy, Edmund Jr., Rep. Annual Report, Field, 5/20/1973-9/10/1974 (Box 59, Folder 881)
  - Worthy, Edmund Jr., Rep., 7/1973-12/1973 (Box 59, Folder 882)
  - Worthy, Edmund Jr., Rep. Correspondence with Ann Walko, 6/1973-5/1974 (Box 59, Folder 883)
  - Worthy, Edmund Jr., Rep. Correspondence, 1/1973-6/1973, 7/1972-12/1972, 1/1974-3/1975 (Box 59, Folder 884-886)
  - Wright, Arthur F. and Mary C. (Trustee), 6/1970 (Box 60, Folder 887)
  - Wright, Dudley of Geneva, Switzerland (Prospective Contributor), 1969-1972 (Box 60, Folder 888)
  - Wuhan Historians Visit, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 889)
  - "Y", 9/2/1964-11/4/1976 (Box 60, Folder 890)
  - Yale Alumni Weekly: Editorial, 3/18/1927 (Box 60, Folder 891)
  - Yale Charities Drive: Contribution to Yale in China, 4/25/1962-11/5/1973 (Box 60, Folder 892)
  - Yale Clubs: Presidents, 8/16/1974-12/1/1974 (Box 60, Folder 893)
  - Yale in China Association: Budget and Treasurer's Reports, 6/13/1960-6/4/1973 (Box 60, Folder 894)
  - Yale in China Office: Correspondence, 1966-1978 (Box 60, Folder 895)
  - Yale in China Association: Minutes of Meetings, 10/27/1964-9/11/1965, 11/21/1965-12/1967, 6/10/1968-6/12/1972, 11/10/1972-11/23/1973 (Box 60, Folder 896-899)
  - Yale in China: Weekend, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 900)
  - Yale Daily News, 7/1965-10/8/1973 (Box 60, Folder 901)
  - Yale University, 1979-1980, 1983-1985, 7/12/1985-6/13/1986 (Box 60, Folder 902-907)
  - Yali Guest House: Chinese Univ. of Hong Kong, 10/2/1971-9/19/1973 (Box 60, Folder 908)
  - Yali Women's Auxiliary: Minutes, 3/17/1916-5/10/1916 (Box 61, Folder 909)
  - Yau, Lee-Ching: Overseas Scholar, 1973-1975 (Box 61, Folder 910)
  - Yen, Keng-Wang: Visiting Fellowship, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 911)
  - Yeung, Tin-Sing: Graduate Scholar, Chemistry, 1970-1972 (Box 61, Folder 912)
  - Yip, Terry Karn Ha: Overseas Scholarship, Business Administration, 1975-1977 (Box 61, Folder 913)
  - Young President's Organization, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 914)
  - Young President's Organization January 1985, 1/7/1985-2/6/1985 (Box 61, Folder 915)
  - Young President's Organization February 1985, 10/1984-4/29/1985 (Box 61, Folder 916)
  - Young President's Organization March-June 1985, 1/4/1985-8/16/1985 (Box 61, Folder 917)
  - Young President's Organization July 1985, 1/27/1985-7/11/1985 (Box 61, Folder 918)
  - Young President's Organization October 1985, 6/6/1985-12/1985 (Box 62, Folder 919)
  - Young President's Organization November-December 1985, 11/4/1985-12/1930/1985 (Box 62, Folder 920)
  - Young President's Organization Briefing Book, 12/1985 (Box 62, Folder 921)
  - Young President's Organization, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 922)
  - Young Women's Christian Assoc., 3/1919-3/19/1923 (Box 62, Folder 923)
  - Yung, Kwan-Chee: Overseas Scholarship, 1976-1978 (Box 62, Folder 924)
  - "Z", 6/14/1972-4/27/1978 (Box 62, Folder 925)
  - Film and audiocassette
    Conditions Governing Access
    Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
    - Chiang Ching Dancers, Undated; 1; 3/4in. Umatic; Run time: 00:42:00 Audio: Mono, Ch1, Ch2 (Box 63)
    - Chinese Musical Instruments: An Introduction, Undated; 1; 3/4in. Umatic; Run time: 00:31:06 Audio: Mono, Ch1, Ch2 (Box 64)
    - Chiang Ching, Undated; 1; 3/4in. Umatic; Run time: 00:31:06 Audio: Mono, Ch1, Ch2 (Box 65)
    - Cabaret: Sir Run Run Shaw Hall, 1985 March 22; 1; TDK cassette; Run time: 01:02:01 (Box 66)
    - The Last Dynasty, Undated; 1; 16mm film; Run time: 00:28:43 Audio: Mono, Optical (Box 67)
    - The Republican Revolution, Undated; 1; 16mm film; Run time: 00:30:23 Audio: Mono, Optical (Box 68)
    - Recruiting film, Undated; 1; Super 8mm film; Run time: 00:23:22 no audio (Box 69)
  - Publications (Box 70)